06/02/2022 17:00 Ana Manuella Ribeiro



# Ana Manuella Ribeiro

Full Stack development student

#### About me

Hi. My name is Ana Manuella. I am in transition of career change to IT field. Currently I am studying Full Stack Development at Infinity School. I have good knowledge in Web Development (HTML, CSS e Javascript) and excellent organizational skills with great attention to detail. I am passionate about design and have good knowledge using Photoshop, Gimp and Lightroom softwares. In addition, I am senior-level management professional with 8 years of solid experience in Customer Service & Hospitality area. I am available right there in the contact section if you want to hear me more.

Email

ana.manuellar@gmail.com

Telefone

+55 27 99589-1897

Cidade

Salvador-BA

127.0.0.1:5500/index.html 1/3

06/02/2022 17:00 Ana Manuella Ribeiro

## **Hard skills**

**HTML** 

CSS

Lightroom

Adobe Photoshop

Gimp

Bootstrap

# **Professional experience**

## General Manager at Accor Hotels

Nov, 2020 - Jun, 2021

### **Deputy Manager** at Accor Hotels

May, 2012 - Oct, 2019

127.0.0.1:5500/index.html 2/3

06/02/2022 17:00

#### **Education**



2021 - now

MBA Management, Entreprerneuship and Marketing at PUCRS

2017 - 2019

### Contact

#### **Address**

CEP 40070-170. Salvador-BA. Brasil

#### **Telephone**

+55 27 99589-1897

#### **Email**

ana.manuellar@gmail.com

A

https://www.facebook.com/amsribeiro

0

https://www.instagram.com/rsmanu30

https://github.com/anamanuellar

127.0.0.1:5500/index.html 3/3